[{"id": 1338, "question": "A cheap drug that can stop bleeding in people recently injured in an accident could potentially save the lives of tens of thousands worldwide, a new study says. Researchers studied the effects of tranexamic acid , or TXA, in more than 10,000 injured people in 40 countries who received the drug within 8 hours of being injured. The study was published in the medical journalLancet.Doctors found that patients who got TXA had a 15percent lower chance of dying from _ than those who didn't get it . They also had a 10 percent lower chance of dying from any other cause, including organ failure and a head injury. The study was paid for by the British government. The drug is commonly used in wealthy countries during elective surgeries to stop bleeding , but isn't used for accident victims. TXA is off...\n\nQ: Doctors were worried about using TXA because   _", "options": ["a lot of patients died unexpectedly after using it", "it has no treatment effect on patients", "it can cause blood clots or stroke", "they hadn't used it on accident victims before"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 922, "question": "It's 2035. You have a job, a family and you're about 40 old. Welcome to your future life. Getting ready for work, you pause in front of the mirror, \"Turn red,\" you say. Your shirt changes from sky blue to deep red. Tiny preprogrammed electronics are rearranged in your shirt to change its color. Looking into the mirror, you find it hard to believe that you are 40. You look much younger. With amazing advances in medicine, people in your generation may live to be 150 years old. You're not even middle-aged. As you go into the kitchen and prepare to pour your breakfast cereal into a bowl, you hear: \"To lose weight, you shouldn't eat that,\" from your shoes. They read the tiny electronic code on the cereal box to find out the nutrition details. You decide to listen to your shoes. \"Kitchen, what c...\n\nQ: How is the text organized?", "options": ["In order of time.", "In order of frequency.", "In order of preference.", "In order of importance."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2347, "question": "Many people keep the stamps in a drawer at home because they'll never know when they might need them! The trouble is that they have no idea of how many stamps they have left. When they want to send something by post, it's very annoying to find out that they have run out of stamps! The Internet is possible to solve the problem. The United States Postal Service has come up with a system which allows people to print their own postage stamps at their own home! This is the perfect solution for those people that have busy lives! Whenever you go to the post office to buy a stamp, you are buying a boring and standard postage stamp. They are red in color, and you can easily buy them on the Internet as well. For example, you can just order a regular 1st class stamp and then print it off using your o...\n\nQ: With the system of the United States Postal Service, people can   _  .", "options": ["buy photo stamps at a very low price", "send their international mails for free", "design their own photo stamps", "have their letters delivered faster than before"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3379, "question": "New rules for pubs and clubs, including a ban on drinking games like the awful \"dentist's chair\", will be introduced in Britain this year to prevent the heavy drinking culture, which costs the country billions of pounds a year. Other activities like \"all you can drink for 10 pounds \", \"women drink free\" nights and speed drinking competitions will also be banned. But, on the other hand, offers of cheap alcohol in supermarkets will not be affected, which is widely regarded as one of the main sources of Britain's problems with under-age and over-drinking. Doctors and health experts argue that the government has failed to use its most effective weapon, the taxation of minimum price controls on alcohol. Home Secretary Alan Johnson said that the government and the industry had a duty to act on h...\n\nQ: According to the passage, \"the dentist's chair\" is   _  .", "options": ["a chair for the patient whose teeth should be treated", "a drinking game made famous by the celebrations of footballers", "a way to advertise different types of alcohol", "to be banned in October this year"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1002, "question": "Zoe Chambers was a successful PR(Public Relations) consultant and life was going well -- she had a great job, beautiful flat and a busy social life in London. Then one evening in June last year, she received a text message telling her she was out of work. \"The first two weeks were the most difficult to live through.\" she said. \"After everything I'd done for the company, they dismissed me by text! I was so angry and I just didn't feel like looking for another job. I hate everything about the city and my life.\" Then, Zoe received an invitation from an old school friend, Kathy, to come and stay. Kathy and her husband, Huw, had just bought a farm in north-west Wales. Zoe jumped at the chance to spend a weekend away from London, and now, ten months later she is still on the farm. \"The moment I ...\n\nQ: How docs Zoe feel about the country life according to the passage?", "options": ["Tiresome and troublesome.", "Romantic and peaceful", "Mentally exhausting but healthy", "Physically tiring but rewarding."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 994, "question": "Most painters discover a style of painting that is fit for them and stick to that, especially if people admire their pictures. But Picasso, the great Spanish painter, was like a man who had not yet found his own particular style of painting. He kept on struggling to find the perfect expression till his death in 1973. Some of Picasso's painting are rich, soft color1ed and beautiful. Others are ugly and cruel and strange. But such paintings allow us to imagine things for ourselves. They force us to say to ourselves,\"What does he see that makes him paint like that?\" And we begin to look under the surface of the things we see.. Picasso painted thousands of pictures in different styles. Sometimes he painted the natural look of things. Sometimes he seemed to break them apart and throw the pieces...\n\nQ: The ugly cruel and strange paintings by Picasso   _  .", "options": ["make us try to notice something latent in the things", "allow us to ask questions about them", "force us to question anything we see", "cause us to think what Picasso saw was different from what we see"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3171, "question": "My student teaching experience was a wonderful adventure. I had to deal with various discipline and behavior challenges that occurred again and again. The greatest part of it was the relationship I developed with two students. One of the students was named Michael,whom I met when I was working for a kindergarten. Before I became a morning bus assistant, I'd heard that Michael was a challenging student who would always shout, stand up on the bus, make fun of other students, and distract bus driver. So I decided that each morning, when he got on the bus, I'd have Michael sit beside me. At first he didn't like this idea and pouted about it. But soon he settled down, knowing he had no choice. I began to talk to him about little things outside of school life, such as his weekend activities and ...\n\nQ: What is the text mainly about?", "options": ["The two greatest students during the writer's career as a teacher.", "The writer's best memories of his teaching experience.", "How to motivate slow students.", "How to deal with naughty students."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 193, "question": "Chances are that you've had to apologize plenty of times in your life. And there's a goodchance that you've also expressed the phrase, \"I never meant to hurt you.\" Stop doing that, says author Caroline Myss. In a talk Myss - a spiritual researcher - took on the topic of forgiveness and healing, and explained in no uncertain terms why \"I never meant to hurt you\" is never a sufficient apology, no matter who it comes from. \"Picture that person coming up to you and saying, 'Wow, l'm sorry I did this, but, you know ,l never meant to hurt you. And, hey, can we just call it a day?\"' Myss says. Though it can make the two bur\\ the hatchet and keep friendship, that type of apology won't sit well with the person on the receiving end. \"That whole little thing - 'I never meant to hurt you' - that's the...\n\nQ: How should we apologize according to Myss?", "options": ["We should confess our faults and ask for forgiveness.", "We should say sincerely \"I never meant to hurt you\".", "We can go into a deep conversation to argue with our friend.", "We are supposed to make up with the other by giving some gifts to him."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 165, "question": "If you had a strange sound in your ear, what would you do? One man in Wales who thought he had a fly in his ear called 999, the emergency services number in Britain. And so did a woman who was worried about her green potatoes. Could she make chips with them? Were they poisonous? She didn't hesitate about calling the local ambulance service to ask. According to a recent report, more than 31,000 non-urgent calls were made to the Welsh Ambulance Service in the last year. Inappropriate calls are a headache for health professionals everywhere. In the US, prank calls to 911 happen on a daily basis. Many callers use apps which hide their identity. But those who try to be funny shouldn't be surprised if the police _ . One man from Colorado was arrested for making more than 1,200 prank calls, accor...\n\nQ: According to the text, prank calls are usually  _  .", "options": ["meant to be helpful", "dealt with in time", "thought highly of", "made to play tricks"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 908, "question": "Travel can be a lifesaver. But in today's economy with airlines adding new fees almost daily and ticket prices sharply on the rise, many have written off travel as too expensive. However, with a few saving tricks and a little research, there are still lots of great deals to be had on airline tickets and more. Early Bird Gets the Deal. Travel experts say that there are certain times of day when more deals are available. Airfares can change three times a day as airlines adjust their prices to fill up flights. Early morning is when the fares tend to be lowest.www.zxxk.com What Wouldn't a Business Traveler do? Flying when business travelers don't can save you big money. Most business travelers fly on Mondays and Fridays, so Tuesday and Wednesday are the best days. Airlines will usually lower t...\n\nQ: Which would be the best title for the text?", "options": ["Tips on Vocation Travelling", "Advice for Business Travelers", "The Effect of Economy on Airlines", "Tricks of Finding the Cheapest Flights"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 543, "question": "Yueyang Tower lies in the west of Yueyang City, near the Dongting Lake. It was first built for soldiers to rest on and watch out. In the Three Kingdoms Period, Lu Su, General of Wu State, trained his soldiers here. In 716, Kaiyuan of Tang Dynasty, General Zhang Shuo was sent to defend at Yuezhou and he rebuilt it into a tower named South Tower, and then Yueyang Tower. In 1044, Song Dynasty, Teng Zijing was stationed at Baling Jun, the ancient name of Yueyang City. In the second year, he had the Yueyang Tower repaired and had poems by famous poets written on the walls of the tower. Fan Zhongyan, a great artist and poet, was invited to write the well-known poem about Yueyang Tower. In his A Panegyric of the Yueyang Tower (<<>> ), Fan writes: \"Be the first to worry about the troubles across t...\n\nQ: Yueyang Tower was once named   _  .", "options": ["South Tower", "Xianmei Tower", "Sanzui Tower", "Baling Tower"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1440, "question": "I'm usually fairly skeptical about any research that concludes that people are either happier or unhappier or more or less certain of themselves than they were 50 years ago. While any of these statements might be true, they are practically impossible to prove scientifically. Still, I was struck by a report which concluded that today's children are significantly more anxious than children in the 1950s. In fact, the analysis showed, normal children aged 9 to 17 exhibit a higher level of anxiety today than children who were treated for mental illness 50 years ago. Why are America's kids so stressed? The report cites two main causes: increasing physical isolation brought on by high divorce rates and less involvement in community, among other things and a growing perception that the world is a ...\n\nQ: Which of the following statements is TRUE according to the passage?", "options": ["To children, anxiety is completely avoidable.", "TV and computer play an important role in isolating children from the real world.", "Exercise does not help to lessen children's anxiety.", "Sometimes local news about crime and murder also affects children a little."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1550, "question": "*200 dead as Brazilian plane crashes in Sao Paulo Up to 200 people were dead after a passenger plane with 176 people aboard slid off the runway on landing and hit a fuel storage tank at Sao Paulo's Congonhas airport on Tuesday. Brazilian airline TAM said that 170 passengers and 6 crew were aboard the Airbus A320 flying from Porto Alegre in southern Brazil to Sao Paulo when it lost control on landing and slid off the wet runway. Brazilian news agency Folha reported up to 200 people were dead, including some victims on the ground. * _ Two people were killed Saturday in two separate plane crashes in the United States, media reports said. In Dayton, Ohio, a plane crashed on a runway of the Dayton International Airport while performing during the Vectren Dayton Air Show. The pilot, Jim LeRoy, w...\n\nQ: It can be inferred from the three news that  _", "options": ["whenthe Airbus A320 landed, it was likely to be raining heavily", "during the Vectren Dayton Air Show , the pilot, Jim LeRoy died on the scene", "The place where the Boeing 737-800 crashed was just 12 miles from the town", "Five Chinese passengers were victims of the Kenya plane crash"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2438, "question": "It is a reply to a letter written by Zhai Mingjun, a 16-year-old girl in the class. The two astronauts thank the student for her concerns and wish the class luck in their future studies. \"I' m so happy that the two space men replied with a few encouraging words,\" said Zhai. Her letter was one of the 10 winning letters taken into space by Fei and Nie, who have succeeded in traveling space in the Sixth Shenzhou Spaceship. Zhai wrote the letter as if she were a younger sister of the astronauts. \"As the single child in my family, I always hoped that I would have an elder brother that I could be proud of,\" Zhai said. \"I thought that the astronauts would be lonely during such a long space trip. I hoped they would feel happy and warm when reading my letter.\" Many of Zhai' s classmates also wrote ...\n\nQ: The passage is mainly about   _  ?", "options": ["what the students think of the manned space program", "how two astronauts thank and encourage the students", "how the letter from space makes the students care more for astronautics", "how the students have expectations for China' s future space program"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1117, "question": "\"Migrant workers\" is a familiar term for 17-year-old Shi Jian. Her father and uncle often talk about the problems surrounding this group of people. However, Shi cares more about the children of these migrant workers. Last year Shi's housekeeper's daughter had to give up her schooling in Beijing because she would not be allowed to sit the national college entrance exam. She was forced to continue her high school education in her hometown in Sichuan Province. Shi thinks the current law is unfair for migrant workers' children, as it prevents them from studying at public schools, unless their parents pay huge sums. So, Shi decided to do a survey of migrant workers so that she could find some solutions to help solve the problem. In the last six months Shi spoke to 186 migrant workers in Beijing...\n\nQ: According to Shi's survey, most migrant workers' kids   _  .", "options": ["don't live together with their parents", "attend schools near their parents' working places", "have to help their parents support the family", "always do better in schools than children from the city."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 619, "question": "\"Mama, when I grow up, I'm going to be one of those!\" I said this after seeing the Capital Dancing Company perform when I was three. It was the first time that my dream took on a vivid form and acted as something important to start my training. As I grew older and was exposed to more, my interests in the world of dance certainly varied but that little girl's dream of someday becoming a dancer in the company never left me. In the summer of 2005 when I was 18, I received the phone call which made that dream a reality: I became a member of the company dating back to 1925. As I look back on that day now, it surely lacks any sense of reality. I believe I stayed in a state of pleasant disbelief until I was halfway through rehearsals on my first day. I never actually expect to get the job. After ...\n\nQ: How did the author feel when she look back on that day now?", "options": ["strange", "unrealistic", "indifferent", "lucky"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 259, "question": "Shopping in the United States changes a lot.About ninety years ago most people shopped in small stores that were owned by one person or a family.Women went from the bakery to the butcher's to the grocer and on to the fruit and vegetable seller in order to get their food for the week. Then about sixty years ago, supermarkets were born.In a supermarket, people could get all the different kinds of food they needed without going to different stores. The next big change in shopping in the United States was the shopping mall.A shopping mall is a group of stores under one roof.Because malls allowed people to shop without worrying about the weather, they soon became very popular.The mall became a place for people to socialize in addition to shopping.If you walk through a mall, you will see older p...\n\nQ: What's the disadvantage of online shopping according to the passage?", "options": ["Wasting time.", "Leaking personal information.", "Fixed prices.", "No chance to do physical activities"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3358, "question": "When American inventor Alexander Graham Bell invented the telephone in 1876, it was a revolution in communication. For the first time, people could talk to each other over great distances. Over the last two decades a new means of spoken communication has appeared: the mobile phone. The mobile phone is like a two-way radio. But the two-way radio is a limited means of communication. As soon as the users move out of range of each other's broadcast area, the signal is lost. In the 1940s, researchers experimented with the idea of using a number of radio masts to pick up signals from two-way radios. A caller would always be within range of one of the masts. When he or she moved too far away from one mast, the next mast would pick up the signal. (Scientists referred to each mast's reception area ...\n\nQ: The article is intended to  _  .", "options": ["warn people of the possible risks in using mobile phones", "inform readers of the history and benefits of mobile phones", "convince people of the uses of mobile phones", "predict the applications of mobile phones"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3093, "question": "How's your relationship with your dad? It can be easy to let walls build up between you during the teen years. But by taking several simple steps, you can help improve the relationship between the two of you--even without great efforts. Here are a few quick tips. Talk it out. Communication is key to any friendship. Open your mouth and let your dad know what's on your mind. Give him a chance to get to know you. Listen up. Your dad's lived more life than you have. Believe it or not, he's probably been there and can help you get through the pressures and struggles. Ask how he dealt with school, girls or temptations . Then pay attention. Take some time. It can be hard for us kids to talk about what really matters. But spending time together can build the relationship, and create chances to tal...\n\nQ: From the passage we can infer that  _  .", "options": ["fathers play an important role in teenagers' growth", "communication can prevent all the disagreements", "talking everything out at once always helps", "teenagers should never get angry with their fathers"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3193, "question": "A long road leads through the woods to Don Robinson's unfinished house. Wearing dirty sneakers and a shirt with holes, Don Robinson is an 81-year-old Missouri businessman. Although he's rich, he didn't use his money to buy himself a grand home. Instead, he used it to buy wild land. Robinson has decided to donate 843 acres of his own personal _ to the Department of Natural Resources after his death, which can then be used to create a new state park. His generous donation is the same size as New York City's Central Park. It is said that it's the largest land donation to happen in the last 25 years. How did he come up with this idea? For Robinson, the idea of donation came from his respect for the land and the environment. He doesn't have children to pass it onto. He hoped that someone would ...\n\nQ: Don Robinson has decided to donate   _   to the Department of Natural Resources after his death.", "options": ["a green park", "a big wooden house", "843 acres of land", "all his money"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 99, "question": "I've done many things that would make any parent proud. I've taken part in sports, community work and school events, but I am most proud to be a good big brother. I have to watch over four sisters and a brother, plus myself. That's quitea task, but one I feel I have gotten good at. My brother needs more attention than most siblings. When he was nine, he was hit by a pick-up truck on the way to the bus stop and lost use of the lower two-thirds of his body. He's been in a wheelchair for six years. My brother does many things, but sometimes he tries to do things he used to do but can't now. I' m always there with words of encouragement. I now watch my brother struggle to do as many things as he can within and beyond his limits. Should he fall, I will be the person to pick him up. I also watch...\n\nQ: The author's brother needs more attention because   _  .", "options": ["he is the youngest child of the family", "he lost the functions of his lower body", "he was disabled by a careless bus driver", "he needs the words of encouragement"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2617, "question": "What is it: Work & Travel USA Who are qualified: Fulltime college students, above 18 years old About the program: Application for the 2009 Work & Travel USA program has just started. It's an 8~16 weeks' summer program for college students to work and travel in the U.S.. Employers include Boeing, Hilton Hotel and 7Eleven. For next summer, about 3,500 positions are open to Chinese students. Applicants must pass a language test and sometimes an interview, and pay a registration fee to join the program. (source : www. Cultureexchange. org) _ What is it: Shanghai Volkswagen jobs Who are qualified: College students graduating in 2009 About it: Shanghai VW offers over 300 positions from engineering to marketing to college students graduating in 2009. Applicants should have an excellent academic r...\n\nQ: If you want to apply for assistant to the director positions you must   _  .", "options": ["be good at document writing", "study computer science", "have communication ability", "be familiar with various languages"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3147, "question": "Working Wives Last week, we published an article about modern marriage. A recent survey showed that in England 51 percent of married women go out to work . people were asked what they thought of \"working wives\". The results were as follow: Men Women In favor 70% 80% Against 10% 20% Don't know 20% 0% We asked readers to write and tell us their opinions. Here are some of the hundreds of letters we received. I'm a (woman)photographer. I make plenty of money, travel a lot, and meet a lot of people. I enjoy my work, and would hate to stay at home. I would never marry a man who wanted me to give up my work. Ms. Jojo O Leary Hampstead At present there are over 1,000,000 unemployed men in Britain. If a woman gets a job, she puts one more man out of work. Perhaps that man has a wife and twelve chil...\n\nQ: The woman photographer would not marry a man who   _  .", "options": ["has less money than her", "likes staying at home", "is not very gentle", "wants her to stay at home"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2766, "question": "What is the color1 of the universe? Astronomers had not answered this question until two months ago. That is when two American astronomers reported on their study of all the light in the universe. They said that the universe would appear to the human eyes to be a light greenish color1. Karl Glazebrook and Ivan Baldry of Johns Hopkins University in Baltimore, Maryland, reported their finding in January. They presented the research at a meeting of the American Astronomical Society. They said that finding the color1 of the universe was not part of their more serious scientific research. They did it for fun. However, earlier this month, the scientists admitted making a mistake. They said their finding was much more color1ful than it should have been. They now say the light from our universe is...\n\nQ: This passage mainly tells us   _  .", "options": ["what the color1 of the universe is", "the light from our universe is a light greenish color1", "the new color1 of the universe is much more color1ful", "the finding of the color1 of the universe is difficult"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2194, "question": "Trans-Bridge Tours is looking forward to providing you with another year of exciting One-Day travel destinations in 2016. Statue of Liberty & Ellis Island August 15 (Sat) $78 Adult; $66 Child (4-12); $ 75 Senior (62+) No visit to the New York City area is complete without a trip to the world's most famous landmarks--- the Statue of Liberty and Ellis Island. Price includes transportation to Liberty State Park and timed ferry tickets. 9/11 Museum& Memorial September 29 (Tue) $ 87 Adult; $ 78 Youth (7-17); Senior $80(65+) The Museum displays artifacts associated with the events of 9/11, while presenting stories of loss and recovery. The Memorial between the twin reflecting pools, is a tribute of remembrance and honor to the nearly 3,000 people killed in the terror attacks. The New York Botani...\n\nQ: Which day will a geological researcher prefer?", "options": ["August 15.", "September 29.", "October 14.", "November 21."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1083, "question": "It's 5pm on a Friday and I'm standing in a coffee shop above Shibuya crossing - one of the most busiest place in Japan where more than a thousand of Tokyo's smartly dressed people gather at eight points, ready to cross - then rush straight for each other. It looks like they must bump into each other, but It's amazing that they all manage to reach the other side safely. But the real reason I'm here is that I want to see people crash. I want businessmen to knock into each other, their umbrellas flying off their arms, and uniformed schoolchildren hitting grannies. Why may I see this now, but wouldn't have had the chance even a year ago? It's very simple - smartphones. Smartphone use is booming in Japan. In 2012, only about a quarter of Japanese used them, most being perfectly happy with their...\n\nQ: After smartphone walking himself, the author thinks  _  .", "options": ["it's exciting to walk while sending emails", "it's really dangerous to walk while sending emails", "there are some others smartphone walking like him", "other passers-by give way to him although they dislike."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2931, "question": "Jones worked so hard that made the sparks fly from his hammer.The son of Mr.Smith, a rich neighbor, used to come to see the blacksmith and he would enjoy himself watching how the tradesman worked.\"Why don't you try your hand to learn to make shoe tacks?\" said the blacksmith.\"Who knows, one day, it may be of use to you.\" The lazy boy began to see what he could do.But after a little practice he found that he was becoming very skilled and soon he was making some of the finest tacks. Old Mr.Smith died and the son on account of the war lost all his goods.He had to leave home and was forced to take up residence in another country.It so happened that in this village there were numerous shoemakers who were spending a lot of money to buy tacks for their shoes and even at times when they paid high p...\n\nQ: The reason why young Smith was forced to leave his home town is that   _", "options": ["he was lazy and wasted all the money from his father", "the price of shoe tacks in another country was high", "his father died and left nothing for him", "there was a terrible which broke his peace"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 148, "question": "Growing up in Philadelphia, Lieberman started cooking with his stay-at-home dad when he was seven. His food-loving family had two kitchens, and he quickly learned what was the best way to bake his cakes. Lieberman improved his kitchen skills during a year abroad beforo college, learning from a cook in Italy and study local specialties in Gerrnany, Spain and France. At Yale,he was known for throwing dinner parties, single-handedly frying and baking while mixing drinks for dozens offriends. Just for fun, he and some friends decided to tape a show named Campus Cuisine about his cooking. Lieberman was a real college student showing his classmate how to do things like making drinks out of dining-hall fruit. That helped the show become very popular among the students. They would stop Lieberman a...\n\nQ: Why did the airline company give Lieberman the job?", "options": ["He could prepare meals in a small kitchen.", "He was famous for his shows on Food TV.", "He was good at using eggs to make sandwiches.", "He could cook cheap, delicious and simple meals."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2020, "question": ". Passage 1 Every morning, when we wake up, we have 24 brand-new hours to live. What a gift! We have the capacity to live in a way that these 24 hours will bring peace, joy, and happiness to ourselves and to others. Peace is right here and now, in ourselves and in everything we do and see. The question is whether or not we are in touch with it. We don't have to travel far away to enjoy the blue sky. We don't have to leave our city or even our neighborhood to enjoy the eyes of a beautiful child. Even the air we breathe can be a source of joy. We can smile, breathe, walk, and eat our meals in a way that allows us to be in touch with the abundance of happiness that is available. We are very good at preparing how to live, but not very good at living. We know how to sacrifice ten years for a di...\n\nQ: The author of Passage 1 would most likely view the author of Passage 2 as    _   .", "options": ["failing to respect the feelings of other people", "squandering a precious opportunity on a daily basis", "advocating an action without considering the consequences", "attaching too much importance to the views of others"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 643, "question": "Earthquakes are something that people fear. There are some places that have few or no earthquakes. Most places in the world, however, have them regularly . Countries that have a lot of earthquakes are usually quite mountainous. The most talked about earthquake in the United States was in San Francisco in 1906. Over 700 people died in it. The strongest one in North America was in 1964. It happened in Alaska. Strong earthquakes are not always the ones that kill the most people. In 1755, one of the strongest earthquakes ever recorded was felt in Portugal. Around 2,000 people died. In 1923, a very strong earthquake hit Tokyo, the Yokohama area of Japan. A hundred and forty thousand people died. Most of them died in fires which followed the earthquake. One of the worst earthquakes ever was in C...\n\nQ: Earthquakes happen  _  .", "options": ["only in a few places along the mountains", "regularly in most places in the world", "in all the places in the world", "only in the countries that have a lot of mountains"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1943, "question": "My description of a hero is a person who _ his all for others. A person who puts others before himself.A person who does ordinary things, not because they have to, but because they want to. So I got to think who are my heroes? Several people came to mind. But there was one that really stuck out in my mind. I guess I really thought about it, but this man really is my hero. This man is my dad. I know,we all think our dads are our heroes. But the truth is, I really can't ever remenber thinking of my dad really as a hero. I am sure that I have said that he was. But I an not sure if I ever really thought about in terms of what is a hero?I mean he never saved anyone's life. He never fought in a war. He never invented anything to make life easier for others. But as I thought of his qualities. I f...\n\nQ: We can infer from the text, heroes in the writer's eyes   _  .", "options": ["must be great man", "can be ordinary people", "must be famous", "must be our fathers"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 352, "question": "I love everything about making Easter dinner except the Saturday shopping. That day, the supermarket can be as crowded as a department store at Christmas. And this Easter, on top of my regular checklist, I had to buy the ingredient for a delicious, new recipe I'd discovered: sliced ham and turkey layered with Swiss cheese and cabbage, all wrapped in pastry dough. Trouble was that my work schedule had left me no time to shop earlier in the week. I would get up extra early and take care of everything on Saturday morning, I thought, as I drove to the office on Friday. But that morning, Yola, one of my co-workers, asked if my husband Robert and I would help her move the next day. \"I really don't have anybody else to ask,\" she apologized. \"Sure,\" I told her, soft touch that I am. Early Saturday...\n\nQ: According to her plan, what was the author going to do on early Saturday morning?", "options": ["Shop in the supermarket.", "Cook some delicious food.", "Do extra work in her office.", "Help her co-worker move."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2607, "question": "More than two thirds of the world's polar bears will be wiped out by 2050,according to a shocking new study. By then,scientists say,global warming will have melted 42 percent of the Arctic sea ice. By 2100,only a very few of these important creatures will be left. The report has been produced by the US Geological Survey. The scientists have publicized their findings in the hope of influencing US Interior Secretary Dirk Kempthorne,who has been asked to put polar bears on the US endangered species list. Polar bears depend on floating sea ice as a platform for hunting seals,which are their main food. Without enough ice,polar bears would be forced to go onto the land,where they are poorly skilled hunters,and would be unlikely to adapt to the life on the land in time. Experts say few little bea...\n\nQ: What do we know about Dirk Kempthorne according to the passage?", "options": ["He is an animal scientist.", "He is a protector of animals working for the US government.", "He was asked to put polar bears on the US endangered species list.", "He offered to put polar bears on the endangered species list."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3298, "question": "Do you feel embarrassed when your mum tries to use slang or when she calls you by your childhood nickname in front of your friends? And how about searching for the nearest exit when your father dances with joy when he finds his favorite CD in the shop? Loving them dearly doesn't prevent you from feeling uncomfortable around them. And parents have to accept that Adam Gopnick, a writer for the New Yorker magazine, said in an article published by the BBC: ''The one thing that is written into the human genome is that exactly at the age of 13, your child... will discover that you are now the most embarrassing, ridiculous and annoying person on the planet.'' A survey by the site YoungPoll.com in 2010 suggested that one in three youngsters is so _ by their parents that they refuse to be seen with...\n\nQ: Why do some children feel humiliated when their parents kiss them in front of friends?", "options": ["Because they don't show enough love for their parents.", "Because they don't want to be treated like children.", "Because their parents are embarrassing, ridiculous and annoying.", "Because they want to grow up."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1977, "question": "We found out that Jenny was suffering hearing loss when she was four and a half years old. Several operations and speech classes later, when she was seven, we found out that Jenny had Juvenile Rheumatoid Arthritis . She could not put pressure on the heels of her feet, so she walked on tiptoe , and when the pain became unbearable, I carried her. Jenny was fortunate, though, because she did not suffer the deformities , often associated with JRA. All through grade school, and on into high school, Jenny suffered, yet never complained. She took her medicine, and I would often wrap her feet in steaming towels, and hold her until the pain eased. But, as soon as she could stand the pain, Jenny, immediately, carried on, as though she were pain-free. She wore a smile on her face, a song on her lips,...\n\nQ: We can learn from the passage that  _  .", "options": ["Jenny was the first girl football player in her school", "the coach was strict with his team members except Jenny", "Jenny did service work on the school football team", "Jenny could go to Charleston College free of charge"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2673, "question": "\"Wake up. Alicia is waiting for you outside,\" my mother called from the kitchen. My mother didn't like me going for this weekend to my friend's house in the mountains. \"I trust you, but I don't trust the people out there,\" she said seriously. \"I'm going to be fine,\" were my last words before closing the door of the Jeep. The vehicle went along the dusty road and my mother grew smaller in the distance. The trip over the rough road was uncomfortable. It was scary to climb the steep hills surrounded by great pines. After a long trip we finally arrived at the house. From the moment I got there I knew I would forever love the house. It was decorated like an old country home. My room was small, yet set up nicely. That night I went to sleep early, not because I didn't want to continue my search, ...\n\nQ: What is the main idea of the passage?", "options": ["Her close friend.", "The peaceful life.", "A favorite trip.", "The distant village."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 462, "question": "Flying Ever since I was old enough to dream,I have imagined myself soaring with the eagles.My love of flying has shaped the way I live and the person I have become.Two years ago,that passion rocketed to new heights when I had the opportunity to visit Embry Riddle Aeronautical University in Arizona.For a whole week I lived in a college dorm,roomed with a total stranger and---best of all---I flew! My group took part in activities ranging from learning about the history of aviation to flying in state-of-the-art pilot training simulators .At least once a day,I devoted myself to learning one of the world's best training aircrafts,the Cessna 182.Not only did I receive thorough ground instruction,but I also got to fly.In total,I flew five hours to receive my private pilot's license. In that one j...\n\nQ: Two years ago,the author  .", "options": ["was admitted to a university", "stayed in a university for one week", "saw the launch of the rocket", "made good friends with an astronaut"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1333, "question": "If the crust of the earth were not pretty solid ,it would be shaking about and moving up and down frequently. However,there are places in the rocks of the earth's crust where it isn't strongly held together--where faults exist. Along the faults,one rock might push against another with great force. The energy is changed to vibration in the rocks,so they begin to shake and we have an earthquake! The most famous one in North America was the San Francisco earthquake of 1906. Seven hundred people died and property damage amounted to about $425,000,000.The greatest destruction came from the fires that followed the quake. One of the most famous earthquakes in Europe took place in Lisbon,Portugal,in 1755.The city was destroyed and at least thirty thousand people were killed. In 1908,in Calabria an...\n\nQ: According to the passage,the earthquake that killed the most people happened in  _  .", "options": ["Portugal", "Italy", "Japan", "China"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1223, "question": "Television in the United States is free. To pay for programs, there are many advertisements. Often these advertisements are short plays with actors. The following television advertisement is like many others that Americans see daily. We see a man and his wife at the breakfast table. They have been married for a long time. They are not speaking to each other. They haven't spoken to each other at the breakfast table for years. The husband is reading his newspaper. We can't see his face. The wife looks very bored as she pours a cup of coffee for him. Today, she is using a new kind of coffee for the first time. The husband picks up his cup. He isn't very interested. He tastes his coffee. Suddenly he puts down his newspaper. Something is different.! Can it be the coffee? He takes another taste....\n\nQ: What does the author mean by saying the last sentence?", "options": ["What kind of coffee can change people's lives?", "How can a new kind of coffee change people's lives?", "Nice coffee can change one's life.", "A new kind of coffee costs quite a lot."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3393, "question": "Since the 1950s, most of the stars of pop music have come from Britain and America. Howver, in the last ten years, when many different kinds of music have established themselves on the pop scene, more and more stars have come from other countries. Pop music changes all the time and new stars appear and become famous. For a musician to stay popular and still produced good, original music over a long period of time, is a sign of true star. Most stars start their careers in a simple way---- playing in unknown night clubs or dance-hall where people want to dance to the music, not listen to it. They may have continued doing this for many years untill they get a \"break\"---- a chance to perform in a well -known place or get a recording contract. To become a star is the aim of every singer or musi...\n\nQ: Since the 1950s,most of the stars of pop music have come from  _  .", "options": ["America", "America and Britain", "America and Europe", "other countries"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 146, "question": "Growing up in Philadelphia, Lieberman started cooking with his stay-at-home dad when he was seven. His food-loving family had two kitchens, and he quickly learned what was the best way to bake his cakes. Lieberman improved his kitchen skills during a year abroad beforo college, learning from a cook in Italy and study local specialties in Gerrnany, Spain and France. At Yale,he was known for throwing dinner parties, single-handedly frying and baking while mixing drinks for dozens offriends. Just for fun, he and some friends decided to tape a show named Campus Cuisine about his cooking. Lieberman was a real college student showing his classmate how to do things like making drinks out of dining-hall fruit. That helped the show become very popular among the students. They would stop Lieberman a...\n\nQ: The Food Network got to know Lieberman  _  .", "options": ["at one of his parties", "from his teacher", "through his taped show", "on a television program"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 784, "question": "Wood Buffalo National Park Wood Buffalo National Park is Canada's largest national park and one of the largest in the world. Established in 1922 to protect the last remaining herds of bison in northern Canada, it now protects an outstanding example of Canada's Northern Boreal Plains. The park was designated a World Heritage Site in 1983. Phone: (780) 697-3662 E-mail: wbnp.info@pc.gc.ca Banff National Park of Canada Banff's rich history dates back to 1885, when three railway workers stumbled upon hot mineral springs surfacing from deep within the mountains. This discovery led to the establishment of Banff National Park, and marked the beginning of Canada's national park system. Spanning 6,641 meadows and rivers, Banff National Park is one of the world's premier destination spots. Phone: (40...\n\nQ: Which of the following is NOT true?", "options": ["Wood Buffalo National Park is famous as one of the largest national parks in the world.", "Banff National Park established because of the discovery of hot mineral springs.", "St. Lawrence Islands' establishment marked the beginning of Canada's national park system.", "Grasslands National Park preserves a part of the mixed prairie grasslands."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 666, "question": "A treasure trove hidden for centuries has been discovered in the underground vaults of a temple in southern India. The treasures include gold, diamonds and precious stones. The estimated value of the hoard is reportedly 22 billion US dollars. Hundreds of armed police have been deployed around the temple. Meanwhile, a debate about how to use the money has also broken out across the country. After discovering the treasure trove in Sri Padmanabhaswamy Temple in the southern Indian state of Kerala, the local government has assured security of the temple. Elaborating on the security arrangements, Venugopalan Nair, Additional Director General of the Kerala Police, says the latest security devices are being used to guard the temple. Venugopalan Nair, Additional Dir. Gen. of Kerala Police, said, \"...\n\nQ: Which of the following is NOT TRUE according to the passage?", "options": ["The treasures include gold, diamonds and some old coins.", "The treasure trove has been lying unknown for hundreds of years before it is discovered.", "The local people are very curious about the treasure and the temple.", "The whole area surrounding the temple is under close watch."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1094, "question": "College visits are important.Before you commit years of your life and money to a school, be sure you're choosing a place,\" that is a good match for your personality and interests.You can't get the \"feel' of a school from any guidebook, so be sure to visit the campus.Below are a few tips for getting the most out of your college visit. 1.Explore on your own Of course you should take the official campus tour, but be sure to allow time to hang around on your own. The trained tour guides will show you a school's selling points.But the 1dest and prettiest buildings don't give you the entire picture of a college.Try to walk the extra mile and get the complete picture of the campus. 2.Read the Bulletin Boards When you visit the student center, academic buildings and residence hall, take a few minu...\n\nQ: The best way to know about a college in an official campus tour is  _  .", "options": ["to walk around the campus alone", "to take pictures of the campus", "to visit the oldest and prettiest buildings", "to hire a tour guide"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1765, "question": "Up, Up, and Away! An adventurer who became the first person to fly across the English Channel on a cluster of balloons has launched a house into the sky just like in the hit movie Up-in reparation for a more ambitious journey and a new record Fearless Trappe , from North Carolina, stepped into the cartoon themed home before flying above the leon International Balloon Festivel in Mexico more than a week ago. The 38-year-old Trappe was using the event as a warm-up for his planned trans-Atlantic flight scheduled for next summer ,He aims to complete the 2,500-mile journey in a seven-foot lifeboat carried by 365 huge helium ballooms The brave man is learning to sail a lifeboat ,in case he meeds to ditch into the ocean during the danger-filled adventure He sill fly at between 18,000 feet and 25,...\n\nQ: How many world records does Jonathan hold?", "options": ["Two", "Three", "Four", "Five"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 81, "question": "The best selling children's book, Pipilu Sending You 100 Lives, has been adapted into a homonymous play that will be put on for the first time next March and tour around 50 cities in China. The book was adapted by the Hangzhou based Star Dream Factory. \"We don't want to descend to the average children's dramas that are overly eager to please the kids,\" said Huang Qin, director of Star Dream Factory. \"We want to provide something practically useful and mystically entertaining.\" The original book by Chinese children's book writer Zheng Yuanjie focuses on safety tips for kids. With Zheng's usual _ and simplicity, the book avoids sugar-coating reality. Instead, it illustrates the potential dangers in everyday life and provides possible solutions. Zheng recalled that when he saw his new-born ba...\n\nQ: The book Pipilu Sending You 100 Lives is trying to tell the readers   _  .", "options": ["how Pipilu give you 100 lives in a clear way", "how Pipilu can live a more interesting life in a simple way", "how we can live a safer life in an understandable way", "how we can have 100 lives in a pleasing way"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2015, "question": "The old lady was glad to be back at the block of flats where she lived. Her shopping had tired her and the basket had grown heavier with every step of the way home. In the lift her thoughts were on lunch and a good rest, but when she got out at her own floor, both were forgotten in her sudden discovery that her front door was open. She was thinking that she must tell her daily maid the next morning to lock the door, and then she remembered that she had gone shopping after the maid had left and she knew that she had turned both keys in their locks. She walked slowly into the hall and at once noticed that all the room doors were open, yet following her regular practice she had shut them before going out. Looking into the living room she saw a sight of confusion over by her writing desk. It w...\n\nQ: The old lady was surprised to find the front door open because   _  .", "options": ["she had told the maid to shut it", "she had shut the door herself", "she saw the maid shut it", "the maid was not usually careful"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1177, "question": "Scientists have exactly discovered the set of brain cells involved in making risky decisions, and have been able to control them in rats using targeted light. By changing the activity of the cells they were able to change the behaviour of risk-taking rats to avoid risk, hinting the approach could in future be used to treat people with impulse control problems. Risk-taking is a key part of survival, knowing when to take a chance could pay off--such as moving to a new area to look for food when pickings are slim. While all animals need an element of risk, the preference towards it varies between individuals. Researchers found this variation, which determines how risk-averse an individual is, is regulated by brain cells in a region of the brain called the nucleus accumbens. This cluster of ne...\n\nQ: The variation in people's preference towards risks is directly regulated by   _  .", "options": ["nucleus accumbens", "light sensitive proteins", "neurons", "dopamine"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 344, "question": "A new survey finds that more than eighty percent of Internet users in the United States search for health information online. The survey found that searching online is one of the leading ways that people look for a second opinion though doctors are still the main source of health information. Forty-four percent of people are actually looking for doctors or other providers when they search for health information online. Another finding of the survey: Two-thirds of Internet users look online for information about a specific disease or medical condition. The Internet has also become an important source of emotional support for people with health problems. Susannah Fox says one in five Internet users has gone online to find other people who have the same condition. It was more popular among pe...\n\nQ: By using social networking, patients with rare diseases can   _  .", "options": ["find effective cures", "get emotional comfort", "ask for financial support", "consult doctors anytime"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1084, "question": "A woman was waiting at an airport one night, with several long hours before her flight. She bought a book and a bag of cookies in the airport shop, and found a place to drop. She was interested in her book, but the man sitting beside her grabbed a cookie or two from the bag in between, which she tried to ignore to avoid an argument. So she ate the cookies noisily and watched the clock, as the cookie thief diminished (......) her stock. She was getting angrier as the minutes passed, thinking,\"Oh, brother, if I wasn't so nice, I would blacken your eyes.\" With each cookie she took, he took one, too. When only one was left, she wondered what he would do. With a smile on his face, he took the last cookie and broke it in half. He offered her half, and he ate the other. She got it from him and th...\n\nQ: Why did the woman ignore it when she found the man eating the cookies?", "options": ["She didn't want to get into an argument.", "She was full of pity for the man.", "The man was dangerous and brave.", "She was too careless to notice it."], "answer": 0}]